Guide to the Albert R. Mann papers, 1916-1931.
Mann, Albert R. papers, 1916-1931.
- Miscellaneous, A-Z Materials, 1916-1931
  - Hills, J. L., 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Jenkins, Charles F., 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Lindeman, E. C., 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Lowman, Seymour, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Machold, H. E. (Assembly Speaker), 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Mann, A. R. (Expenses), 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Mann, A. R. (Expenses), 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Mann, A. R. (Personal), 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Morrisville School of Agriculture, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - New York Milk Conference Board, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - New York Milk Conference Board, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - New York Milk Conference Board, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - New York Milk Conference Board, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - New York Milk Conference Board, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - New York Milk Conference Board, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Phi Kappa Phi, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Printing, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 70)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 71)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 72)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 73)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 74)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 75)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 76)
  - Statistics, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 77)
  - Supplies, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 78)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 79)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 80)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 81)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 82)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 83)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 84)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 85)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 86)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 87)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 88)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 89)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 90)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 91)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - White, Horace, 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Witter, Daniel P., 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Y Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Z Miscellaneous, 1921-1922 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Adler, Senator Simon L., 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Blauvelt, George A., 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Blauvelt, George A., 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Bailey, L. H., 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - Bills, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Butterfield, K. L., 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Convention Commission, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Dairymen's League, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1922-1923 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ferris, Senator M. Y., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Frame, Nat T., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Hills, J. L., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Lindeman, E. C., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Lowman, Senator Seymour, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Lusk, Senator Clayton R., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Machold, Assemblyman H. E., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Mann, A. R., Expense Accounts, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Morrisville State School, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Official Record, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Official Record, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Pearson, Raymond A., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Pearson, Raymond A., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Pearson, Raymond A., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Printing, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Q Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Robinson, James R., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Statistics, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Straus, Senator Nathan, Jr., 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Wessels, P. H., 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - White, Horace, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Witter, Assemblyman, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Witter, Assemblyman, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Y Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Z Miscellaneous, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1922-1923 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Adler, Simon L., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Bailey, L. H., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Building Matters, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Building Matters, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Butterfield, K. L., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Blauvelt, George A., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Cobleskill State School, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Conservation Commission, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Dairymen's League, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Farmingdale, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Farmingdale, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Farmingdale, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Farmingdale, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - G.L.F. Exchange, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Hills, J. L., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Hills, J. L., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - International Institute of Agriculture, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Lusk, Clayton R., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Land Economics Institute, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Lowman, Seymour, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Legislative, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Machold, H. E., 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - Mann, A. R. - Expense Accounts, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 61)
  - Mann, A. R. - Personal, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 62)
  - Morrisville State School, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 63)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 64)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 65)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 66)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 67)
  - Positions Wanted, 1923-1924 (Box 31, Folder 68)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Q Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Robinson, James R., 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Straus, Nathan, Jr., 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Supplies, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - White, Horace, 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Witter, D. P., 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Wessels, P. H., 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1923-1924 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1923-1924 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1923-1924 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Y Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Z Miscellaneous, 1923-1924 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Abstracts, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 80)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 34, Folder 81)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Bailey, L. H., 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Cobleskill State School, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Dairymen's League, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Extension Service News, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Farm Economics, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Farmingdale, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Farmingdale, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - GLF Exchange, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Hills, J. L., 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Legislative Index Publishing Company, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Morrisville, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Q Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Robinson, J. R., 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Rose, Wickliffe, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Rose, Wickliffe, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Straus, Nathan, Jr. (Senator), 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Statistics, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Supplies, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - White, Horace, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Witter, Daniel P., 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Y Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - Z Miscellaneous, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 63)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 64)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 65)
  - Betten, Cornelius - Expense Account, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 66)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 67)
  - Cobleskill State School, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 68)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 69)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 70)
  - E Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 71)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 72)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 73)
  - Farmingdale School, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 74)
  - Farmingdale School, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 75)
  - Farmingdale School, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 76)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 77)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 78)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 79)
  - Home Economics, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 80)
  - Hutchinson, C. B., 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 81)
  - Hutchinson, C. B., 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 82)
  - Hutchinson, C. B., 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 83)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 84)
  - J Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 85)
  - K Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 86)
  - L Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 87)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 88)
  - M Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 89)
  - Morrisville State School, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 90)
  - Morrisville State School, 1925-1926 (Box 36, Folder 91)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Mann, A. R., Personal, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - N Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - O Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - P Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Pearson, R. A., 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - R Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Robinson, James R., 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Rose, Wickliffe, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - S Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Supplies, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Shepardson, Whitney H., 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Shepardson, Whitney H., 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Shepardson, Whitney H., 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - T Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - U Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - V Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - W Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - White, Horace, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - White, J. DuPratt, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Witter, D. P., 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Westervelt, J. C., 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Z Miscellaneous, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - A Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - B Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Butterfield, K. L., 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Butterfield, K. L., 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - C Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - Cobleskill, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - D Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Dairyman's League, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - Eastman, E. R., 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - F Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Farmingdale, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - G Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 59)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  - H Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 63)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 64)
  - I Miscellaneous, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 65)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 66)
    Lund, Wallace
    Brierley, W. W.
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 67)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 68)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 69)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 70)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 71)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 72)
    Rose, Wickliffe
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 73)
  - International Education Board, 1926-1927 (Box 39, Folder 74)